Joseph Adrien Munoz

Creative Director, Graphic Designer, Photographer

Covina, CA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Joseph-Adrien-Munoz/be07db2e047a7a98

Creative professional with fifteen years of experience in private, commercial and corporate industries, specializing in graphic design, photography, brand care, social media management and art direction.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Creative Director

Bridgetown Church - Monrovia, CA - April 2016 to Present

Create all graphics (Print and web) for Advertising, Marketing and Social Media Content needs / Create photo content with live photography and scheduled shoots each week / Photo Editing / Social Media Management, creating and preparing all content for Instagram, Facebook, Instagram Stories, Snapchat / Execute all print file set up, prepare and send out all printing jobs / Web programming, Updating website with new content on Wordpress / Organize and lead street teams for event promotion / Plan advertising and marketing strategies with team for general visibility and special events / Create brand looks for each study series / Create video graphics for various video needs / Copywriting

Graphic Designer/Art Director

Substance Over Hype, EFG - North Hollywood, CA - November 2014 to Present

Develop vision with each music artist through graphic artwork and photography, used for Album art, Single art, Poster art and Social media content / Create graphic artwork for each advertising campaign for music artist and company / Create and develop brand look for Elite Frequency Group, including Logos and general art direction for company / Photography, live and studio shoots, including all photo editing needs / Web Programming, building and updating all website needs on Wordpress platform

Graphic Designer (Freelance)

Roots NYC Church - Long Island City, NY - September 2016 to May 2017

Create all graphics (print and web) for advertising, marketing and social media content needs / Editing photos in Lightroom and Photoshop provided by team to be prepared for all social platforms / Social Media Management, including curating the visual direction, preparing all text content and posting artwork and photos to communicate a visual story / Prepare and send out all print jobs / Web programming, build up website on Wordpress platform, create and manage new content / Copywriting

Art Director/Graphic Designer (Freelance)

Boihawk - Los Angeles, CA - August 2006 to August 2016

Under my creative signature Boihawk, I was contracted to develop Logos, Posters, Album Artwork, Single track artwork, Advertising Campaigns, Advertising and Marketing materials (brochures, flyers, banners, trade show display art, apparel, business cards, large format print) / Film poster illustrations / Photography / Photo Editing / Video Graphics / Brand Care / Art Direction / Website programming / Social Media management and content creation / Event Coordination including planning live events with touring artists / Talent booking / Team management / Nightclub management

Graphic Designer/Photographer

Armando Custom Cases - Hesperia, CA - January 2012 to November 2014

Revise creative direction for company with new Logo, new brand direction and assets / Create graphics for website, advertising campaigns, tradeshow events, social media and mailchimp e-mail newsletters and promos / Product photography and photo editing / Social Media Management, creating and uploading content to Facebook and Instagram / Design and send out all Print jobs / Tradeshow booth design, including mapping out overall look of booth and creating all display art / Copywriting / Web programming, designing, creating and updating all website needs on Wordpress

EDUCATION

Diploma in General Education

Chaffey Adult School - Ontario, CA January 2001 to January 2001

SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop (10+ years), Adobe Illustrator (10+ years), Adobe Dreamweaver (10+ years), Adobe InDesign (3 years), Copywriting (10+ years), Photography (5 years), Photo Editing (10+ years), Social Media Management (10+ years), Wordpress (10+ years), MailChimp (6 years), Advertising (10+ years), Event Coordination (10+ years), Typography (10+ years), Print (10+ years), Design Layout (10+ years), Video Graphics (10+ years), Microsoft Office (10+ years), Windows OS (10+ years), MAC OS (2 years), Marketing Communications (10+ years)

LINKS

http://imaculthero.com

http://www.armandocases.com

http://www.boihawk.com

http://www.bridgetownchurch.us

http://www.instagram.com/cult.hero

http://www.instagram.com/rootsnycchurch

http://www.instagram.com/sheepoverwolves

http://www.rootsnyc.church